这样吧  穿这个  唇色用酒红色
I'm thinking, with this, if we have burgundy lips,
你知道吧  头发往后梳紧
you know, hair pulled back tight...
-用银色可以吗  -好的  我明白了
-Can I get the silver? Okay, okay. I got it.
你  好吧  可以了
You... Okay. All right.
你好  贾斯汀  抱歉打扰你
Hey, Justin, sorry to bother you.
我其实在研究薇薇安的裙子
I was actually looking at some of Vivian's dresses,
然后我画了一些草图  你可以帮我看一下吗
and I drew up some sketches I'd love for you to take a look at.
你干好自己的本职工作就好
Please just stick to the chart.
好的  但是我觉得这个点子很棒
Okay, but they're, like, cool ideas.
就是  我是说  我想
Just... I mean, I think.
-听我说说  -亲
-Just hear me out. -Honey,
我们请你来不是让你来思考的
we're not paying you to think.
大家好  我们很荣幸
Hey, everyone, it's our pleasure
邀请到薇薇安 陈重返洛杉矶时装周
to welcome Vivian Chan back to Fashion Week Los Angeles.
好了
Okay.
继续吧
Keep it going.
明白
Got it.
妆画的不错
Makeup went well. It had...
你知道的  这风格曾经流行过
You know, it had its moments.
苏苏
Suzu.
在路上了吗
You on your way?
是啊
Yes.
我偷了两大包化妆品
And I stole two bags of makeup.
你一定会赢这场选美比赛
Yeah! You are winning this pageant.
当然了  因为我有你这个秘密武器
Of course. 'Cause you're my secret weapon.
好莱坞大名鼎鼎的化妆师
My Hollywood makeup artist.
好的  爱你  开车不聊了  拜拜
Okay, I love you. I'm driving. Bye.
欢迎来到墨西哥
Welcome to Mexico.
谢谢
Gracias.
苏苏
Suzu.
瞧瞧我们
Look at us.
我比你发育的早多了
I grew boobs way before you did.
但是我现在还在发育期啊
Girl, I'm still trying to grow boobs.
那倒是
That's true.
明天选美的事几点开始啊
Hey, what time do we start that pageant thingy stuff tomorrow?
明早9点
9:00 in the morning.
光是排练就整整花了3天
Then there's rehearsals for three days.
-然后还要试裙子  -苏苏
-Then fit the dresses. -Suzu!
在阳台
Balcony!
我饿了
I'm hungry.
歌莉娅
Gloria!
我最喜欢的小鲜肉
There's my favourite little dude.
-不算小了  你都长大了  -是啊
-"Little"? You're huge. -Yeah.
你终于回提华纳了
You finally came back to Tijuana.
是啊  我还给你带了礼物
Yeah, and I brought you something.
是什么
What is it?
我的天啊
Holy shit!
噘嘴猫
Potty mouth.
这个我在好莱坞见过
It's the one we saw in Hollywood!
我还以为你忘了
I thought you forgot about it.
-我怎么会  -我觉得你应该
-Come on. -Well, you should practice
跟歌莉娅多练练英语  别让她白来一趟
your English with Gloria. Take advantage.
是她应该多练练西班牙语呢  这样
She should practice Spanish. Maybe she won't
她就不会一开口就暴露自己是逊逊的美国人了
sound like a lame American.
他说的很对
He's right.
呃哦  姐姐  你好大的啤酒味啊
Guácala, sister. You smell like beer.
好了  弟弟  我给你做了土豆汇香肠
Okay, little brother. I made you papas con chorizo.
放在微波炉里了
It's in the microwave.
你好  下午好
Hello, good afternoon.
在这里签名
Sign here please.
你呢
You?
不是  我只是陪朋友来的
No, I'm... I'm not registering.
我不这么认为
I didn't think so.
你说什么
What did you say?
-我就是跟她说  -你不能这样跟我的朋友说话
-I'm just saying to her... -You cannot talk to my friend like that.
好了 苏苏  好  别放心上
Okay, Suzu. Yeah, vámonos.
-好运哦  -谢谢
-Good luck. -Thank you.
你怎么总是喜欢跟人吵架
You always get into fights.
-如果我赢了  -当你赢了之后
-If I win this thing... -"When" you win this thing.
当我赢了之后
When I win this thing,
那我跟察瓦的生活将会大有变化
it's gonna be really good for Chava and I.
当然了
Sure.
就这样  自然的眼妆加上个深色的唇色
Okay, so I went with a very natural eye and a dark lip.
修饰一下
Touching up.
就做了一点改动
Just a little different,
就完全不一样了
but you're done.
好啦  我有东西给你
Okay. I've got something for you.
友谊手链
Friendship bracelets.
得了吧
Stop it.
这样好幼稚啊
Like when we were kids.
戴好了
There you go.
我特别开心你能来这
Hey. I'm so happy that you're here.
你知道吗  我本来觉得我
You know, I didn't really think
不可能再回到提华纳了
I was gonna be able to come back to Tijuana.
因为我觉得我完全不属于这里
'Cause I always felt like such a stranger here.
但是你总是让我觉得我在这里是有家的
But you always make me feel like I have family,
所以我要谢谢你
so thank you.
傻妞  你就是我的家人啊
Girl, you are my family.
没错
Yes.
好了  我们得走了  准备惊艳四座吧
Okay, we need to get going, 'cause we got people to impress.
你来吗
Are you coming?
真的吗  好  小心点
Really? Okay. Careful.
我认识他
I know him...
别这样
No.
好吧
Okay.
姐们  别说你没看到他
Dude, tell me you saw him.
看到了
Yes.
干杯
Cheers.
可以请你跳舞吗
Shall we dance?
抱歉  不行
No. No.
好吧
Okay.
所以我们到底是来跟谁混脸熟的
So, who do we have to rub elbows with?
我们赶快行动吧
Let's get it moving.
那边  就是他
Over there. That's him.
那个就是绍赛多局长
Okay, that's Chief Saucedo.
都说比赛就是他出资搞的
He supposedly finances the contest,
据说他会跟赢得选美比赛的冠军上床
and they say he sleeps with whoever wins the pageant.
那你还想赢吗
And you're still trying to win this pageant?
小妞  这只是个传言
Girl, it's just a rumour.
-恶心  -你才恶心  小妞  我们过去吧
-Ew. -"Ew," you. Girl, let's go.
这个可爱的小姐姐是谁啊
And who's this lovely girl?
这是我朋友歌莉娅
This is my friend Gloria.
绍赛多局长管理着警察局
Chief Saucedo runs the state police.
那只是我的个人爱好而已
That's just my hobby.
我对生活真正的激情在于美的追求
My real passion in life is beauty.
不好意思  等一下
I... Will you just give me one minute?
我想去趟洗手间
I have to go to the bathroom.
检查一下格间
Check the stalls.
里诺
Lino.
求求你
Please. Please.
要什么都拿走
You can have everything.
求求你
Please. Please.
都给你  要什么都给你
Take it all. You can have everything.
你是美国人吗
You're American?
想活命吗
Do you want to stay alive?
想
Yes.
你没见过我们
You never saw us.
过来
Come on.
绍赛多在贵宾区
Saucedo is in the VIP section.
你有10秒钟的时间离开这里
You got 10 seconds to get out of here.
跑吧  外国妞
Salte, gringa.
嘿  苏苏
Hey. Suzu!
苏苏
Suzu!
Suzu! Suzu!
苏苏
Suzu!
苏苏  求你了  快接电话
Suzu, come on, please. Pick up.
有人要刺杀绍赛多局长
...assassination attempt on Chief Saucedo...
天啊
God.
不好意思  不好意思  先生
Excuse... Excuse me, sir.
我朋友在里面
My friend is inside.
你不能进去  你不能进去
All right, you can't come in here. You can't come in here.
-好好好  -走  走开吧
-No, okay, okay, okay, okay. -Go. Go.
你正在呼叫苏苏  请留言
This is Suzu. Leave your message.
苏苏  我在千年俱乐部对面的餐厅
Suzu, I'm at the diner across the street from the Millenium Club.
听到留言到这里来找我  好吗
If you get this, please meet me here, okay?
提华纳市安吉利斯医院
Hospital Angeles Tijuana.
我想找从千年俱乐部送去的一个朋友
I'm trying to find a friend who was in the Millenium Club.
你朋友的名字是什么
What's your friend's name?
苏苏 拉莫斯
Suzu Ramos.
稍等
Let me check.
没有这个名字
Nobody by that name has been admitted.
察瓦
Chava.
是我  歌莉娅
It's Gloria.
你们什么时候回来啊
When are you guys coming back?
是这样的  苏苏的电话没电了
You know what, Suzu's phone died,
她让我给你打电话
so she just wanted me to call you
告诉你我们可能会晚点回去  好吗
and tell you that we're gonna be a little late, okay?
跟她说我要从她的梳妆台里面拿钱吃午餐了
Tell her I'm taking the lunch money from her dresser.
好的
I will.
-拜  -拜
-Bye. -Bye.
抱歉打扰
Excuse me.
我找不到我的朋友了
I can't find my friend
我需要你的帮助
and I need your help, please.
你得去警察局报案  填写失踪报告
You have to go to the station. Fill out a report.
是这样  我昨晚在千年俱乐部
Okay. I was at the Millenium Club last night,
看到了那些行凶的人  我
and I saw the men who did this, and I just...
我真的需要你的帮助
I really need your help.
好吧  上车
Fine. Get in.
谢谢
Thank you.
说吧  姑娘
Go ahead, se?orita.
昨天晚上都发生了什么
Tell me everything that happened.
有一群人带着枪闯进洗手间
These guys came into the bathroom with guns.
其中有一个头发两侧剃掉了
One of them had the sides of his head shaved.
还有一个眼睛是绿色的
Another one had green eyes.
等一下
One second.
我现在的位置需要有人替班  我这有个美国人
Twenty, I'm here with a forty-one. An American.
她说昨晚见过千年俱乐部的那些人
Says she saw the men at the Millenium.
我跟老大确认一下
Let me check with Number One.
好  等候指示
Copy. Standing by.
我们到了警察局之后
When we get to the station,
我希望你把看到的所有事情都说出来
I want you to tell them everything you saw.
快要到了
We are almost there.
我先下车取我的午餐
I'm just going to pick up my lunch.
再准备一辆卡车
Prep the other truck.
你好吗  唐娜 露西塔
How's it going, Do?a Rosita?
欢迎来到露西塔之家
Welcome to Casa Rosita.
他在里面等你
He's inside.
我的祖父母在40年代建了这座房子
My grandparents built this house back in the '40s.
这是我哥哥
That's my brother.
他想卖掉它  但我想留给我的家人
He wants to sell it, but I want to keep it for the family.
你们应该搞错了
This is a mistake.
我只是想找我朋友
I only wanted to find my friend.
你要是说谎  小心我揍你
You tell me lies, I'm going to hurt you.
听明白了吗
Okay?
我不说谎
I'm not gonna lie.
你是缉毒局派来的吗
You with the DEA?
不是
No.
你口音像美国佬
You talk like a pocha.
你是干什么的
What's your deal?
我在美国长大
I grew up in the States.
我在这生活过几年
I... I lived here for a few years.
我爸爸是美国人
My father is American,
他经营一家工厂  在边境处的一家加工工厂
and he owned a factory, a maquiladora, here.
工厂在哪
Where's the maquiladora?
已经关了
It's gone.
你爸爸呢
And your father?
过世了
Gone, too.
那你为什么来这里
Then why are you here?
我只是来看望我朋友
I just came to visit my friend.
苏苏  苏苏 拉莫斯
"Suzu. Suzu Ramos."
这些东西我要替你保管一段时间
I'm gonna keep these for a while.
好吗
Okay?
我可以帮你找你的朋友
I can help you find your friend.
但是你必须先帮我做一件事
But you have to do something for me first.
你帮我做这件事  我就帮你找苏苏
You do that, and I'll help you find Suzu.
你要是不老实  我就把你们俩个都杀了
You mess around, and I'll kill you both.
-说是  -是
-Say "yes." -Yes.
很好  靓妹
Okay, chula.
我们会成为很好的朋友的  我们俩
We're going to be real good friends, you and I.
你去过贝克斯菲尔德吗
You ever been to Bakersfield?
贝克斯菲尔德吗
Bakersfield?
是的
Ey.
贝克斯菲尔德  在加利福尼亚州
Bakersfield, California.
没去过
No.
我老家是贝克斯菲尔德
I'm from Bakersfield.
我也是美国人  跟你一样
I'm American, like you.
也在两个地方长大  跟你一样
Grew up in both places, like you.
卡车准备好了
The trucks are ready.
把扬声器打开  听我指令
Leave that on and follow my instructions.
好了  跟上来  小妞
All right, stay with us, pochita.
快开  跟上
Come on, keep up.
-别管红灯  -什么
-Run the light. -What?
赶快  跟上  别降速
Come on, keep up! Keep up! Don't slow down.
好了  前面拐角右转
All right, turn right on this corner.
车停在马路边
Park the car real close to the curb.
拿着你的电话  来坡上找我们
Take your phone and meet us up the hill.
嘿
Hey.
干的不错  靓妞
Good job, chula.
车开的不错
Nice driving back there.
吐坎  把遥控器给我
Tucán. The remote.
看着  小妞
Watch this, bitches.
看看这个杰作
Check this out, chula.
厉害吧
What?
别难过啊
Don't be sad. Hey.
那些贱人自找的
Those bitches had it coming.
她好像不喜欢烧烤
Seems like she doesn't like barbecue.
我们快离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
你昨晚去千年俱乐部干什么
What were you doing last night at the Millenium?
陪我朋友  她想参加选美比赛
My friend, she wanted to get connected for the pageant.
加利福尼亚选美小姐吗
The Miss Baja California pageant?
对
Yes.
我们在选美比赛上有认识的人吗
Who do we know at the pageant?
行了  想办法解决这件事吧
Okay. Figure it out.
我们为什么来这里
Why are we here?
你说你想参加比赛
You said you wanted to be in the contest,
所以现在你参加了比赛
so now you're in the contest.
我  那个  我想要的不是参加比赛
I... That's... That's not what I want.
我想要的是找到我的朋友苏苏  这是我唯一想要的
I want to find my friend Suzu. That's what I want.
我们会找到你的朋友的  不用你废话
We'll find your friend, chingada madre.
你可以用这个联系我
You can reach me with this.
别丢了
Don't lose it.
也不要关机
Don't turn it off.
带她去报名  波罗
Take her to register, Pollo.
不用硬拽着她
Let go of her arm.
祝你玩的开心
Have fun.
把你的左侧转过来  好吗
Can I see your left profile, please?
现在转到右边
Now the right?
很好  转回来吧
Very good. Face forward.
姑娘们  让我们欢迎歌莉娅参加比赛
Girls, let's welcome Gloria to the contest, please.
你见过我的朋友苏苏吗
Have you seen my friend, Suzu?
没有  我很抱歉
No. I'm sorry.
-洗手间在哪里  -在走廊的尽头
-Where's your restroom? -It's down the hallway.
好的
Okay.
我就不能自己去洗手间吗
Can't I just have a second
给我点私人空间  可以吗
to go to the restroom in privacy, please?
-你还好吗  -我不好
-Are you okay? -No.
打扰一下  等一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
你是美国人吗  帮帮我  我也是美国人
Are you American? Please, I'm... I'm an American.
我被绑架了  他们在追我
I've been abducted. They're chasing me.
你干什么  你们要干什么
What are you doing? What are you doing?
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no! No!
为什么给我戴手铐
Why am I in handcuffs?
为什么我会在这里  这是哪  我可是美国公民
Why am I here? Where am I? I'm an American citizen.
我被绑架了  求求你
I've been abducted. Please.
你为拉埃斯特雷利亚工作多久了
How long you been working for La Estrella?
我根本不知道你在说什么
I don't know what that is. I don't know what you're talking about.
我是来找我的朋友苏苏的
I'm looking for my friend Suzu.
她在千年俱乐部失踪了
She went missing at the Millenium Club.
我叫歌莉娅 富恩特斯  我是
My name is Gloria Fuentes. I'm an...
我知道你是谁  知道你做什么的
I know who you are. I know who you are.
你是歌莉娅 富恩特斯  1991年出生
You're Gloria Fuentes, born in 1991.
你的职业是
You're a...
化妆师
A makeup artist.
你是里诺 埃斯帕扎的女朋友吗
Are you Lino Esparza's girlfriend?
你根本没在听我说
You're not listening to me.
我是美国公民  我知道我的权利
I'm an American citizen. I know my rights!
我要求被带到美国大使馆去
I want to be taken to the US embassy!
领事馆已经知道你的事了  歌莉娅
Consulate already knows about you, Gloria.
我叫布瑞恩 瑞奇
My name is Brian Reich,
是禁毒署的探员
and I'm an agent with the Drug Enforcement Administration.
这些加密的无线手机
Now, these are encrypted radio cell phones
只有埃斯帕扎和他的同伙在在用
that only Esparza and his people use.
谁都跟踪不到这些手机
They can't be tracked.
现在  你告诉我他给了你一个
So, you're telling me that he gave you one of these
可他甚至都不认识你
and he doesn't even know you?
这是你吗
Is this you?
我当时不知道车里有炸弹
I didn't know that there was a bomb in the car.
是因为这个你才和里诺混在一起吗
Did it make you feel important to be hanging out with Lino?
-什么  不是的  -我理解你
-What? No. -I get it.
你是个无名小卒
You're a nobody from nowhere.
-来自破碎的家庭  -不是的
-A broken home. -No.
你一无所有
You have nothing.
这时你遇到了这个狡猾的家伙
Then along comes this slick guy.
他就像是在向你炫耀他很有钱似的
He's, like, flashing money around,
他在给你钱花
and he's giving you toys
-给你买新衣服  -不是的  不要再说了
-and nice dresses. -No, please.
-他来自提华纳  你刚好也住在那里  -不是这样的
-He's from Tijuana. You lived there... -No.
和他在一起还挺开心的  对吧
He sounds like a fun time, right?
我与此事无关
I didn't have anything to do with this.
求你了  你一定要相信我
Please, you have to believe me.
-好吧  看着  -你一定要相信我
-Okay. Look. -You have to believe me. Please.
你看  你看  你看啊  看啊
Look, look, look, look.
你炸毁的那栋楼是禁毒署的安全屋
The building that you blew up is a DEA safe house.
-不  -看看他们
-Okay, no. -Look at 'em.
看看  看着这些人
Look. Look, look. Look at these guys.
-现在  三个禁毒署的探员  -不
-Now, three DEA agents... -No.
因为你而死了
...are dead because of you.
看看他们  看啊
There they are. Look at 'em.
-不  -看看他们
-No. -Look at 'em.
他们是我的朋友  是真正的美国人
Those are my friends. Those are real Americans.
我们可以  以恐怖袭击  谋杀和纵火的罪名起诉你
We have you on charges of terrorism, murder, arson.
你知道你会被判多久吗
You know how long you'll go away for?
三十年  四十年  五十年
30, 40, 50 years,
除非你帮助我们
unless you help us.
这是一个跟踪芯片
This is a tracking chip,
把它放在电池槽内  就像这样
and it goes in the battery shelf, like this.
你试试看
You try it.
来吧试一试
Go ahead.
继续
There you go.
完美
Perfect.
就是这样
Bingo.
你要把这个芯片
You are taking this chip
放在里诺 埃斯帕扎的手机里
and putting it in Lino Esparza's cell phone.
不
No.
不  请不要再逼我回去了  求求你
No, please don't make me go back there. Please.
听我说  歌莉娅  我希望是你所说的是实话
Look, Gloria, if what you say is true, and I hope it is,
但是你必须证明给我看
you're gonna have to prove it.
所以  拿着芯片
So, you're gonna take that chip
无论如何都要把它安在他的手机上
and plant it on his phone however you can.
从现在开始  你不帮我们
Now, if we don't hear from you,
我就会告诉里诺  说他那里有一个禁毒署的间谍
then I'll make sure Lino knows he has a DEA mole in his group.
如果你敢从他身边逃跑
And if somehow you manage to escape him,
我就会把你扔进美国监狱
I'll feed you to the US prison system.
歌莉娅  这是你的手机
Gloria, here's your phone.
在他们集体检查时  要确保里面没有芯片
Make sure there's no chip in it when they gather for checkup,
不然这就是我们最后一次见到你
or else it'll be the last time we hear from you.
这是我的手机号码
This is my phone number.
记住它
Memorise it.
他们会想知道
They're gonna want to know
你去了哪里  所以
where you've been this whole time, so just...
就告诉里诺你害怕了  逃跑了  好吗
Just tell Lino that you got scared and ran away, okay?
你准备好了的话就开机
Whenever you're ready, just turn it on,
他会马上找到你的  好吗
and then he'll find you, okay?
给你打车钱
For a taxi.
听我说
Listen to me.
有一场战争将在提华纳爆发
There is a war going on right now in Tijuana.
你能否活下来  完全取决于你自己
Whether or not you survive is entirely up to you.
如果你帮我们暴露里诺的位置  我就会把你安全地带离此地
You give us Lino's location, I will get you out of here safe.
那我的朋友苏苏呢
What about my friend Suzu?
我是你和你朋友之间最清晰的道路
I'm the clearest path between you and your friend.
如果你还想再见到她的话
You ever want to see her again,
那就做好你该做的事
you better do what you need to do.
祝你好运
Good luck.
苏苏
Suzu?
察瓦
Chava?
嘿  歌莉娅
Hey, Gloria.
察瓦  你回来了
Chava? You're home.
你旧手机是怎么回事
What's with your old-ass phone?
连游戏都没有
It doesn't even have games on it, dude.
别乱动  把手机给我
Shh, give me the phone.
把手机给我
Give me the phone.
歌莉娅
Gloria?
不要再关机了
Don't ever turn off the phone again.
歌莉娅  你怎么了
Gloria, what's happening?
露皮塔阿姨还住在市中心吗
Does your Tía Lupita still live downtown?
苏苏去哪了啊  歌莉娅
Where's Suzu, Gloria?
我姐姐在哪里
Where's my sister?
苏苏会没事的
Suzu's gonna be fine.
听我说  一切都会好起来的
You hear me? Everything's gonna be fine.
我现在需要你去收拾些衣服
I just need you to go pack up a bag of clothes.
这样吧  我和你一起去  我们一起收拾吧  快点
You know what, I'll go with you. Let's go do this. Come on.
我去给你叫车  楼下见
I'm gonna call you a cab. Meet me downstairs.
-好吗  -好的
-Okay? -Okay.
你为什么逃跑
Why did you run away?
我害怕了
I was scared.
你最好别对我撒谎
You better not be lying to me.
那是你儿子吗
Is that your son?
不  他是我的养子
No, it's my godson.
求求你不要伤害他
Please don't hurt him.
你好啊
Hi.
多乖的孩子啊
What an elegant kid.
过来  过来
Come here, come here.
你有手机吗
Do you have a cell phone?
好吧
Okay.
好的  好的  好的
Okay, okay, okay.
现在
Now,
你回到自己的房间去  好吗
you go back to your room, okay?
这不是我的房子
It isn't my house.
回你屋里待着  在那里等着我
Go to your bedroom. Wait for me over there.
回屋待着  听到了吗
Go to your room! Okay?
我跑了一整天
I've been running all day.
帮我把靴子脱了
Take my boots off.
帮我一下
Please.
请不要伤害那个孩子
Please don't hurt the kid.
你要我做什么我就做什么
I'll do whatever you want.
请不要伤害他
Just please don't hurt him.
好啊
Well,
有件事我需要你帮我做
there is something that I need you to do.
你为我做事
You do that for me,
我自然会确保孩子的安全
and I'll make sure the kid's safe.
可以
Okay.
我们这就是说好了呗
We have a deal?
是的
Yes.
那你现在把衣服脱了
Now, take off your clothes.
什么
What?
把衣服脱了
Take your clothes off.
继续
Go on.
怎么了
What?
里诺
Lino.
我不相信那个女人
I don't trust that woman.
他们不会找她的  她是一个美国人
They won't be looking for her, an American,
是一个混血的美国人
a gringa.
你担心禁毒署找我们麻烦
You worry about the DEA,
我担心她反水
I'll worry about her.
鲁本死了
Ruben's dead.
带着这些钱去参加葬礼吧
Take these pesos for the funeral.
躺下来
Lay down.
当年在贝克斯菲尔德
Back in Bakersfield,
我还是惠特尼高中的学生时
at Whitney High,
我遇到了一个女孩  你很像她
I met a girl like you.
萨曼莎
Samantha.
那是她的名字
That was her name.
萨曼莎
Samantha.
她很漂亮
She was pretty.
和你一样
Like you.
她不爱笑
Never smiled.
也和你一样
Just like you.
歌莉娅
Gloria.
你要开车去圣地亚哥
Hey, you're gonna drive to San Diego.
到我发在导航上的这个地方去
To the address that I put on the GPS.
当你到达边境时  你必须确保
When you get to the border, you got to make sure
你能直视海关的眼睛
that you look at the customs guys in the eyes.
别做傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
回来的路上给我们打电话
When you're on your way back, just call us.
我们会告诉你在哪里碰面
We'll tell you where to meet.
你说过你不会伤害孩子的
You said you wouldn't hurt the kid.
那么  就把他送走吧
So then, send him away.
求你了
Please.
这辆车会带你去露皮塔阿姨家  好吗
This cab's gonna take you to Tía Lupita's, okay?
跟着那个孩子
Stay with the kid.
察瓦  看着我
Chava, look at me.
我会找到苏苏的
I'm gonna find Suzu.
好吗  我向你保证
Okay? I promise you.
别忘了系上安全带
Don't forget to put on your seat belt.
听着  混血妞
Listen up, gringa.
不管任何原因
If, for any reason,
不管是意外还是人为
whether it's an accident or intentional,
如果你带着我们的东西逃走了
you get caught running away with our stuff...
或者你做了别的什么蠢事
Or if you do anything stupid.
我就会拿着这把刀
I'm gonna grab this knife,
像杀鸡一样把那孩子给宰了
and I'm gonna gut that little kid like a chicken.
知道了吗
Got it?
知道了
Got it.
路上注意安全
Drive safe.
路径导航为您服务
The route guidance will start now.
我在干什么  我在干什么啊
What am I doing? What am I doing?
早上好  早上好  今天怎么样
Buenos días, good morning. How we doing today?
-没事  我很好  -你怎么了
-I'm okay. I'm good. -What's wrong?
你比没事可好多了  你刚醒来
You're better than okay. You woke up today.
-你可真幸运  -是啊  你说的对
-You are blessed. -Yeah. You're right.
你知道吗  明天可不是所有人都能拥有的
You know, tomorrow's not promised to anyone.
醒来本身就是最大的祝福了
Just waking up, it's a blessing within itself.
-你说的对  -但是看啊  女士
-You are right. -But look, ma'am.
我只是来这为你打气加油的
I'm just here to cheer up your day.
但这些猫头鹰可以
These owls right here will look at you
在晚上注视着你入眠
at night and watch you sleep.
-不用了  谢谢  -好吧
-I'm good, gracias. -Okay.
没错  继续  把他们带进来吧
Yeah, go on, bring 'em in.
女士  请下车
Ma'am, I need you to step out of the car, please.
请转过去  女士  手背过来
Turn around, ma'am. Manos atrás, please.
你好
Hi.
护照
Passport.
-欢迎回来  -谢谢
-Welcome back. -Thank you.
继续直走  接近目的地
Continue straight ahead to destination.
熄火
Turn it off.
解开
Open it up.
-剩下的在哪  -在车底下
-Where's the rest? -Under the car.
副驾座那边
On the passenger side.
进来吧
Come on in.
你把这辆货车开走
You take the van.
都在这了
It's all there.
我要你给里诺捎个口信
I need to get a message to Lino.
你在听吗
Are you listening?
我要你告诉他
I want you to tell him
吉米说  他的人里有个缉毒局的间谍
Jimmy said the DEA has a mole in his operation.
你听懂了吗
You got it?
明白
I got it.
滚吧
Get out of here.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂
Hello?
在斗牛场的停车场见  就在边境附近
Meet us at the bullring parking lot, right over the border,
走坎特拉街的出口
and take the Cantera Street exit.
知道了
Got it.
好  我要给谁打电话来着
Great. Who do I call?
-喂  -我有东西给你
-Yes. -I've got something for you,
但我想先确保你会保护我
but I want to know that you'll protect me.
我说了  我会的
I said I would.
你在圣地亚哥做什么
What are you doing in San Diego?
他们让我帮他们运武器
They had me pick up weapons for them.
在哪卸货
Where's the drop-off?
-斗牛场的停车场里  -在提华纳吗
-The bullring parking lot. -In Tijuana?
好  我们这就去斗牛场
Okay. We're heading to the bullring.
我们要抓埃斯帕扎
We want Esparza.
如果他在那  就用信息给我发个ox
If he's there, send me a text message with the word "ox."
除非你亲眼看到他  否则不要给我发信息
Do not send a message until you have visual confirmation.
我怎么出来
How do I get out?
通往海边的出口旁边有个黄色双开门  到这来
Get to the double yellow gates next to the ocean exit,
门外会有一辆特警车 他们会带你出去的
and there will be a SWAT van on the other side to pull you out.
明白了吗
You got it?
黄色双开门  知道了
Double yellow gates. Got it.
那是波罗
That's Pollo.
留意下周围的情况
Keep your eyes on the perimeter.
前面那辆越野车
Front SUV.
看到里诺就立即开枪
As soon as you see Lino, take the shot.
这姑娘可能会被乱弹击中
The girl could get hit in the crossfire.
我说了  开枪
I said take the shot.
小心  老大
Watch out, boss!
该死
Shoot.
行动  开始行动
Move in! Move in!
趴下  快走
Stay down! Move it!
不  不
No. No!
救命啊
Help!
接电话  接电话  快接啊
Pick up. Pick up. Pick up.
喂
Hello?
-干什么  -没人来接应我
-What? -There's no one here to get me.
我没看到人  外面也没有特警车
I don't see anyone. There's no SWAT van.
对不起  歌莉娅  你得靠你自己了
Sorry, Gloria. You're on your own.
不  不
No! No!
掩护我  奇沃
Cover me, Chivo!
不
No!
奥马尔
Omar.
快走
Go!
用榴弹发射器
Grenade launcher!
地面二分队  别让他们跑了
Ground Force Two, do not let them out!
小心手榴弹
Grenade!
在墙那里把他们拦下
Cut them off at the wall.
靠
Fuck!
该死的外国佬
Pinche gringa.
那些警察怎么知道我们会去那
How did the state police know we would be there?
你知道吗
Do you know?
他们怎么会准备的如此精密
How were they so ready?
他们居然有狙击手
They had a sniper.
你这个小婊子
You bitch!
嘿  别叫她婊子
Hey! Don't you call her a bitch.
好吗  她刚救了我的命  伙计
Okay? She saved my life back there, man.
因为她别无选择
Because she had to.
听说我  里诺
Listen to me, Lino.
有人跟缉毒局通风报信了
Someone is giving information to the DEA.
-他说的没错  里诺  -什么
-He's right, Lino. -What?
吉米让我告诉你  有个缉毒局的间谍
Jimmy told me to tell you that the DEA has a mole.
一个叛徒  在  在你的组织里
A traitor in your... In your group.
这都是你的错
This is your fault.
什么
What?
我告诉过你要干掉布瑞恩 瑞奇
I told you to get Brian Reich.
我确实干掉瑞奇了
But I did kill Reich.
告诉过你要处理好缉毒局
Told you to handle the DEA.
那是你的工作
That was your job.
我们死的人算你头上
Our dead men are on you.
是你害死他们的
Their blood is on your hands.
你要哭了吗
You gonna cry?
我们从朋友那借到这个地方
We borrowed this place from some friends.
你看起来糟透了
You look like shit.
去找件衣服穿吧
Find some clothes.
他们这应有尽有
They got some good stuff.
我很幸运
I got lucky.
布瑞恩 瑞奇是谁
Who was Brian Reich?
你怎么知道这个名字
How do you know that name?
你刚才说的啊  我
You said it earlier. I...
他是缉毒局的人
He's with the DEA.
那个混蛋
That piece of shit.
没错  但刚才开枪射我们的是警察
Yeah, but that was the police shooting at us.
不管是瑞奇还是绍赛多的人  都一样
Reich or Saucedo's guys, it's the same thing.
都不干净    他们是冲着我来的
They're all dirty, and they're coming after me.
知道吗  我曾经掌管整个提华纳地区
See, I used to run Tijuana,
全世界最大的边境区
the biggest border in the world.
所有进出的东西都得先经过我们
Everything that came in and out came through us,
这就是我们洛星帮
Los Estrellas.
但现在  绍赛多想从我这夺走它
And now, Saucedo is trying to take it from me.
你觉得我是坏人吗
You thought I was a bad guy?
我只是以牙还牙罢了
I'm just playing their game, chula.
-那为什么  -提问到此结束
-So, then why would... -That's enough with the questions.
到厨房帮忙去吧
Go help in the kitchen.
嘿
Hey.
我是伊莎贝尔
My name is Isabel.
开始切菜吧
Start chopping.
所有人上交手机
I need all your cell phones.
你在这做什么
What are you doing here anyway?
你是里诺的女人吗
Are you Lino's girl or something?
他上你了吗
Has he had you yet?
里诺绑架了我
Lino abducted me,
他们威胁我  说要杀死我朋友的弟弟
and they're threatening to kill my friend's little brother.
这就是我在这的原因  可以了吗
That's why I'm here. Okay?
我也不是自愿待在这的
I didn't choose to be here, either.
他们威胁我的家人
They threatened my family.
他们占有了我
They own me.
不要相信他们说的任何话
You cannot trust anything they say.
你的手机呢
Your phone?
给  你这混蛋
Here's my cell, asshole.
忘了你的朋友吧  歌莉娅
Forget your friend, Gloria.
没人会来救你的
No one's coming to save you.
你的手机
Your phone.
我们只是在清扫房间
We're doing some housecleaning.
波伊托是这的仆人
Pollito here is the maid.
他很擅长清除这件事  你懂我的意思吧
He's real good at cleaning, you know?
好香啊  宝贝
Smells good, baby.
你的手机呢
Where's your phone?
在这
Right here.
好
Okay.
继续切啊  歌莉娅
Keep chopping, Gloria.
切  切
Chop, chop.
好
Okay.
好  好了  快好了
Okay, okay, okay.
不
No.
嘿
Hey.
求你了  求你了  求你了
Please, please, please, please, please.
妈的
Shit.
好了
Okay.
你去哪了
Where were you?
你干什么去了
What were you doing?
我去厕所了
I was just in the bathroom.
发生什么了吗
What happened?
你就这么猴急着要上床吗
You couldn't wait to get laid?
你干什么去了  汤都烧干了
What are you doing? The pozole is ruined.
找出那个间谍
Find that mole.
起床了
Get up.
走
Walk.
-你要带我去哪  -就快到了
-Where are we going? -We're almost there.
停
Stop.
如果你再遇到  我们昨天遇到的事
If you run into a thing like we ran into yesterday,
你必须得学会保护你自己
you gotta learn how to defend yourself.
你得学会用这个
You gotta learn how to use one of these.
从它开始吧
Here's an erre.
AR-15步枪
An AR-15 rifle.
产自美国
Made in the USA.
按住这个按钮
Press on this button here.
这个是弹匣
It's a magazine.
子弹  这些是子弹
La bala, the bullet.
子弹能解决所有问题
La bala settles everything.
把子弹装进弹匣
You pop it into the magazine right here.
然后把弹匣装回去
Then you slide the magazine back in.
上膛
Then you pull the charging handle.
这是保险栓
Here's your safety.
拨下去  解除保险
Thumb down, safety off.
拨上来  锁上保险
Thumb up, safety on.
学会了吗
All right?
这次你来
Now you try it.
快点
Come on.
你不会总是像昨天那么幸运的
You're not gonna be as lucky as you were yesterday.
不不不  不对
No, no, no, no, no.
先卸弹匣
Magazine first.
很好
There you go.
你得扣动扳机
You got to press it.
好
All right.
顶住肩膀
Against your shoulder.
不不不  不对
No, no, no.
两只眼睛都得睁开  好吗
You got to keep both eyes open, okay?
你得用视力好的那只来瞄准
You got to use your dominant eye.
因为如果不这样  如果你闭错眼
'Cause if you don't... 'Cause if you close the wrong one,
那你就看不到目标了
then you're not gonna be able to see your target.
重来
There we go.
两只眼睛都睁开
Keep both eyes open.
给你
Here.
再试一次
Try it again.
击中那些酒瓶
Empty it out.
苏苏的事怎么办
What about Suzu?
我派了维丘在查
My boy Wicho is on it.
他是我的技术人员  能力一流
He's my IT guy, and he's real good.
他查过医院和停尸房了
He's checked the hospitals and the morgues,
没找到她  所以说明她还活着
and she's not there, so that means she's alive.
听着  我说过我会找到她的
Listen, I told you I'd find her.
现在  我
For now, I'd...
我想让你先去冲个澡
I'd like you to take a shower.
你喜欢吗
You like it?
我们这是去哪
Where are we going?
里诺
Lino.
Lino!
我们刚烤好
We just finished the barbecue.
太棒了  我饿了
Perfect, I'm hungry.
我给你留了张桌子  在那
I have a table for you over here.
见到你真是太高兴了
It's so great to see you.
你看起来好瘦  怎么不多吃点啊
You look really skinny. Why don't you eat?
你以前吃过烤肉吗
You had barbacoa before?
不行
Nah.
肯定不如这个
Not like this one.
试试
Come on.
-给  -我不饿
-Here. -I'm not hungry.
你肯定饿了
You got to be hungry.
怎么样
So?
好吃
It's good.
只是好吃吗
Just "good"?
我就知道
That's what I thought.
你就应该这么吃烤羊肉才对
That's how you eat some barbacoa, güey.
这就对了嘛
That is what I am talking about.
我不客气了
Let's go.
你知道吗  我在这里长大的
I grew up around here, you know?
一直到我六七岁的时候才离开
Till I was about six or seven.
我来到美国后还会时不时梦到这里
I used to just dream about this place when I was back in the US.
我非常想回到这里
I wanted to come back so bad.
你懂那种感觉吗  就感觉像是
You know, I just never felt like
这里是我的根啊
I belonged anywhere.
然后我和我妈妈被驱逐出境
Then my moms and I got deported,
但当我回来时  墨西哥人看我像个外国人
and when I was back, I was too gringo to be Mexican,
我看他们也像是外国人
too Mexican to be gringo.
所以没办法  我必须硬气一些
So, I had to be tough.
我慢慢学会如何得到我想要的
And I learned to get what was mine.
总有一天  我要买下这附近的所有土地
One day, I'm gonna buy all the land around here.
打算在这里建一个大农场
I could just build a big ranch.
靠这片土地和满地的肥料生活着
Live off the land and shit.
嘿
Hey.
我们找到告密者了
We found the snitch.
大家都在等你
Everybody's waiting.
这婊子还挺有脾气的
Bitch had it in her battery.
伊莎贝尔
Isabel.
洛星帮绝不容忍
Los Estrellas will not stand
任何叛徒和胆小鬼
for cowardice or treason con cualquiera.
别  不要
No, no.
别  别
No, no, no.
奇沃
Chivo.
不  不  别这样
No, no, no, no, no.
让我跟他解释  里诺  别这么做
Let me just talk to him. Lino, no!
不能这么做啊  不能
You can't. No.
让我跟他说一句话
Please let me talk to him.
求你了  别拦着我了
Please. Let me go back.
求求你让我过去吧
Let me go back, please.
不要
No.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
听我说  小妞
Listen, chula.
有时为了生存  你不得不弄脏自己的手
Sometimes, you have to do terrible things to survive.
只有这样  未来才会有希望
Tomorrow's gonna be better.
我保证
I promise.
睡一觉吧
Just get some sleep.
好受些了吗
Feeling better?
今天对你来说可是个大日子
You have a big day ahead of you.
唐娜 露西塔来了哦
Do?a Rosita is here.
嗨
Hey.
米拉  看这件
Mira, this.
这件配你会很搭的
This will fit you just right.
穿上试试看吧
Try them on.
-什么意思  -这都是为你准备的
-What? -These are for you.
一切都是为了今天
Okay? For today.
你想从我这里得到什么呢
What do you want from me?
你到底想干什么
What do you want?
-冷静点  小妞  -不  我没法冷静
-Calm down, chula. -No, I'm not going to calm down.
听明白了么  我想知道你到底要作什么妖
All right? I want to know what this is all about!
赶紧告诉我  告诉我你到底想干什么
I want to know! Tell me what's going on!
嘿  冷静点  你可是我的心肝宝贝
Hey, hey. You're gonna be my queen.
我要送你去参加  加州小姐的选美大赛
I'm gonna send you to the Miss Baja California pageant.
什么  你说什么
What? What?
不要  我不会去参加的
No. No, I don't want to do this.
不行  我真不想去
No. I don't... I don't want to go.
我不想再呆在这里了
I want to leave right now.
-先听我说  -我不听
-Listen to me. -No.
想让我听你说吗  我不会的
Listen to you? I can't.
我不会听的  我再也不会听你的鬼话了
I can't. I can't do this any more.
到头来你就会
You're just gonna end up killing me
像杀了那个女人一样杀了我  对吧
like you killed that other woman, okay?
不如你给我个痛快吧  动手吧
So, just kill me, then!
-我要离开这儿  -求你听我说完
-I want to go. -Please! Listen to me.
我不听  你放开我  你放开
No! Just let me go! Let me...
别挡着我  行吗
Get out of my way!
有些东西需要你先看一看
There's something you need to see.
谁给你这个的
Where did you get this?
你知道拉斐尔 绍赛多是谁吗
You know who Rafael Saucedo is?
到底谁给你这个的
Where did you get this?
我问你  知道拉斐尔 绍赛多是谁吗
You know who Rafael Saucedo is?
知道  他是警察局长
Yeah, he's the chief of police.
是个腐败的垃圾
He's also a corrupt piece of shit.
你朋友在他的手里
He has your friend. Yeah.
那些警察在枪战之后把她带走了
The police, they took her the night after the shootout.
他们公然卖淫  办淫乱聚会
They run girls, throw parties.
他们一直都在这么做
They always have.
你到底从里弄到这个视频的
Where did you get this from?
维丘
Wicho.
他假扮成一个嫖客  警察就把录像发了过来
He posed as one of the johns, and they sent him that video.
呵
Yeah.
他们要她参加绍赛多的聚会
They're offering her up for Saucedo's after-party.
那帮人把她都订满了
They got her all booked up.
她可忙着呢
She's all busy.
一整晚呢
All night.
我也不想给你看这个的
Sorry you had to see this.
你得做出决断了
You can decide.
绍赛多是我的敌人  正如他也是你的敌人一样
Saucedo is my enemy, as he is yours.
至于你的朋友
And your friend,
她今晚会去参加聚会的
she's gonna be there tonight.
同样今晚也是把她捞出来的良机
Tonight's your chance to get her back.
该怎么做
How?
绍赛多总是邀请选美冠军参加他的聚会
Saucedo always invites the winner of the pageant to his party.
我要他单独呆在卧室里
I need him alone in the bedroom.
不对
No.
不对  你是  你是要让我
No. You... You want me to...
我要让他能有机会对你为所欲为
I want you to do whatever it takes.
这是能捞出你朋友的唯一办法
This is how you get your friend back.
奇沃会全程协助的
Chivo will be with you the whole way.
现在
Now,
现在我要你记住我说的话  小妞
I need you to listen carefully, chula.
为了达成这个目的
For this to work out,
你必须相信自己生而为冠军
you need to believe that you belong up there.
你只需要看起来自信满满就行了
You just have to look confident.
我这边买通了裁判
We bought the judges.
甚至买通了整个场子
Everyone works for us now.
好好加油
Play your part.
欢迎来到加利福尼亚选美小姐现场
...Miss Baja California.
你能做到的
You can do this.
就当是为了你的朋友
For your friend.
最后留下的三个决赛选手是
Our three finalists are
玛丽琳 马丁内兹
Marilyn Martínez,
歌莉娅 富恩特斯
Gloria Fuentes,
梅琳娜 唐娜
Melina Do?a.
现在让我们揭晓
And now presenting...
第二名是
the second runner up...
台上剩下两名选手了
There are only two contestants left
但只有一人能问鼎加利福尼亚选美小姐的宝座
and only one can be Miss Baja California.
第一名是
The first runner up...
当主持人说出你的名字的时候  装得惊讶点
When they call your name, act surprised.
本届加利福尼亚选美小姐是
The new Miss Baja California...
歌莉娅 富恩特斯
Gloria Fuentes!
好了  接下来这步最关键
Now, this is critical.
当你被宣布获胜时  一个男人会走向你
Once you've won, a man will come to you
带着绍赛多的口信  邀请你参加他的聚会
with a message from Saucedo, inviting you to his party.
到时候笑着应下来就行了
Just smile and accept.
好啦  幸运儿  让我们送上热烈的掌声
Okay, fotos, finalistas, por favor.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
-能听清吗  -能
-Can you hear me? -Yes.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
准备好了
I'm ready.
我会全程通过这个装置提供帮助
I will guide you through this device.
这样我可以听到周遭的一切声响
I can hear everything through it.
说话的时候记得大声点
Just speak loud enough.
一旦你上了那辆车  我就没法保护你了
Once you get in that car, we won't be able to protect you.
我们认为派对地点在罗萨里多南部的一处房产里
We think the party's on one of the properties south of Rosarito.
加利福尼亚选美小姐
Miss Baja California.
歌莉娅
Gloria.
我们有各种提供高级陪护服务的女孩
We have girls from all the top escort services.
找到绍赛多之后邀他进屋
Get Saucedo to invite you to his room.
加利福尼亚选美小姐
Miss Baja California.
别  叫我歌莉娅就好
Please, call me Gloria.
你能赏脸真令鄙舍蓬荜生辉啊
What an honour to have you here.
您可过谦了  局长阁下
You are too sweet, General.
我想问一下
I have a question.
这漫漫长夜  您过的还舒服么
How's your evening going?
或许还能更舒服一点
Everything is good.
小姐  请随我来
Miss, will you follow me?
在这等着  过几分钟我带你进屋
Wait here. In a few minutes I'll take you next door.
明白我的意思吗
Do you understand?
我需要屋子的方位
We need that location.
-102号别墅  -收到
-Villa 102. -Got it.
保护好自己
Protect yourself.
祝你好运  小妞
Good luck, chula.
哦  天啊
Oh, my God.
我的天啊  我找到你了
I found you. Oh, my God.
我终于找到你了
I finally found you.
我的天啊  我以为你已经死了
Oh, my God, I thought you were dead.
他们伤害过你吗
Are you hurt?
你还好吗  到底发生什么了
Are you okay? What happened?
他们  枪战后他们把我带走了
They... They... They took me after the shootout.
他们把我领进车里  然后
They led me into a car, and...
我以为他们是警察  你知道吗
I just thought they were cops, you know?
他们逼我做那种事
They made me do things, chinita.
他们给我说  不听话就会伤害察瓦
They told me they would hurt Chava.
他们把我卖到淫窝里
They sold me into the system.
还给我打上了这个
They gave me this.
什么
What?
洛星帮
Los Estrellas.
是里诺做的
Lino did this.
你在这干什么呢
What are you doing here?
不是告诉你在那边等着了吗
I told you to wait over there.
跟我进屋吧
Let's go next door.
不好意思
Sorry.
何等动人的女子
What a beautiful girl.
这件红裙衬得你更美了
This red dress turns me on.
把衣服脱了吧
Take off your dress.
咱们喝点酒助助兴
I'll get you a drink.
我跟你说了  把衣服给我脱光了
I told you to take off your dress.
你是不是听不懂人话
Don't you understand me?
Lino Esparza要来杀你  我们要逃出去
过来
Hey.
躺床上去
Get in the bed.
里诺  这边发现绍赛多
Lino, Saucedo is here.
惠州  榴弹发射器
Huicho, grenade launcher.
救救我
Help me.
歌莉娅
Gloria!
苏苏
Suzu?
Suzu!
快走
Come on.
苏苏
Suzu!
Suzu?
是你吗  歌莉娅
Glo? Gloria.
走
Go!
别动
Don't!
歌莉娅
Gloria.
打得好  小妞
Nice job, chula.
你这头该死的猪
Piece of shit.
你算是完成任务了
You got to finish the job.
苏苏
Suzu.
你看
See?
我就说你会把你朋友捞出来的
I told you we'd find your friend.
伸出手来给他看看
Show him your hand.
你一直都知道她在哪里
You knew where she was all along.
我做了我必须做的事情  小妞
I did what I had to do, chula.
我们都是
We both did.
两只眼睛都睁大看着
Both eyes open.
苏苏  我们走
Let's go, Suzu.
昨晚在一场激烈的枪战中
Last night in a fierce gun battle,
尊敬的绍赛多局长被杀害了
esteemed Chief Saucedo killed
同时里诺 埃斯帕扎
Lino Esparza,
洛星帮的匪首也被确认死亡
head of the criminal organization, Los Estrellas.
绍赛多局长壮烈牺牲之前
Saucedo died heroically,
还试图解救数名女性人质
trying to free a group of female hostages.
吉米
Jimmy.
我不可羡慕你的处境  歌莉娅
I don't envy your position, Gloria.
没有纹身没佩刀  我几乎认不出你了
I almost didn't recognise you without your tattoos and your knife.
上次圣地亚哥仓库一别
You've changed a lot
可真是刮目相看啊
since I saw you in that warehouse in San Diego.
你是个幸存者
You're a survivor.
活着走出了枪林弹雨
Walking out of a shootout like that.
妈的
Shit.
这就说通了很多事情
Making it through any of the things
看你过去几天的经历简直是
you've been through in the past few days is...
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想要一杯咖啡
I want some coffee.
你来一杯不
You want some?
看起来你这一晚上可忙的很啊  歌莉娅
Looks like you had a busy night, Gloria.
你杀了一个黑帮老大  还有提华纳的警察局长
You killed a cartel leader and Tijuana's chief of police.
用的可是你们的枪
With your guns.
像你这样的人对我们很有用
Someone like you could be very useful to us.
在此之前你要先提供点好处
I think I'm gonna need something from you first.
我要求被立刻释放
I want to be released immediately.
清除所有案底
Cleared of all charges.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
察瓦
Chava!
歌莉娅
Gloria!